I don't wanna look like an idiot.
I wanna blend in.
If you wanna blend in...
(Sheldon:)...I'd think looking like an idiot
would be the perfect camouflage.
Sheldon, teach me football.
It'll be fun.
(Sheldon:)That's exactly what my father said.
"Come to the games.
Watch the games."
(Sheldon:)Week in and week out,
from the time I was 5...
(Sheldon:)...until I went off to college.
Longest seven years of my life.
(Leonard:)Please, I'm asking you as a friend.
(Sheldon:)Are you making this
a tier-one friendship request?
(Howard:)-Yes.
-Fine.
(Leonard:)-I really appreciate this.
-Yeah, yeah.
(Sheldon:)All right, poindexter,
sit down, shut up and listen.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry?
Oh, that's how my father
always began our football conversations.
(Sheldon:)And if you'd like, after the game,
I'll teach you...
(Sheldon:)...how to shoot close enough
to a raccoon that it craps itself.